<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Record Of My Youth</title>
    <link>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Record Of My Youth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:39:29 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>To Me In Junior Year Of High School</title>
      <link>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/recordofmyyouth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:39:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/recordofmyyouth/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, how are you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From what I remembered at this exact date and time you&amp;rsquo;re in the middle of your extreme diet and as of right now I would say that it backfired as my body can no longer handle normal diets anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But besides that fiasco, I wish you would loved yourself more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You rely your self worth on external sources, which affects your mood, your diet, and your motivations. And I honestly think you&amp;rsquo;re really annoying and very sporadic with your emotions, I wish you weren&amp;rsquo;t like that. But I need to give you some grace since you&amp;rsquo;re just a 17 year old that isn&amp;rsquo;t in an emotionally stable environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Hey, how are you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From what I remembered at this exact date and time you&amp;rsquo;re in the middle of your extreme diet and as of right now I would say that it backfired as my body can no longer handle normal diets anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But besides that fiasco, I wish you would loved yourself more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You rely your self worth on external sources, which affects your mood, your diet, and your motivations. And I honestly think you&amp;rsquo;re really annoying and very sporadic with your emotions, I wish you weren&amp;rsquo;t like that. But I need to give you some grace since you&amp;rsquo;re just a 17 year old that isn&amp;rsquo;t in an emotionally stable environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now where am I going with this? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. I just wish that you handled your relationships better, right now I feel the effects of it even until now. And it is quite dreadful. But i&amp;rsquo;ve been doing better. One thing I miss about you is your motivation and consistency, it&amp;rsquo;s definitely something that I need to regain. I think I am much happier with a consistent schedule, having nothing to do makes me spiral a bit too much. But besides that, I feel like i&amp;rsquo;m learning all the things I would have learned if I were to be in a healthy environment when I was your age. I want to continue to grow, I feel like i&amp;rsquo;ve been much more self-assured lately and that the universe is leading me towards something great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently bought tarot cards and they have been heavily aligned with what&amp;rsquo;s going on with my life right now. Though something it did warn me from is to beware of repeating old cycles and I might be struggling with that a bit, but I know that each day I am getting better and better. I would like to say that I am happier than ever but I&amp;rsquo;m still unsure. I&amp;rsquo;ve been making new friends, seeing friends, and have started to do things a bit more independently. Independence is really important, I felt like it was something i&amp;rsquo;ve lost throughout these past few years. Only recently was when I started growing out of the shell of seeking external validation. Despite this whole thing being a struggle, I&amp;rsquo;m glad to have become even more aware of patterns and instances that i&amp;rsquo;ve learned from and can now avoid in the future. I am happy to have grown as I am today, and I hope I have made you proud.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Day</title>
      <link>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 22:39:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/second-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had a good day today. I was visited by a friend of mine and I showed them around my hometown! It made me realize how fortunate I am to live where I am and I am once again thankful to my parents for relocating us in a city with many fruitful opportunities and activities. I could say that I would&amp;rsquo;ve been better off if I stayed back in my birth[place but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t change it for the world, my lived experiences taught me a lot about love and perseverance - despite always struggling with it lol.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I had a good day today. I was visited by a friend of mine and I showed them around my hometown! It made me realize how fortunate I am to live where I am and I am once again thankful to my parents for relocating us in a city with many fruitful opportunities and activities. I could say that I would&amp;rsquo;ve been better off if I stayed back in my birth[place but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t change it for the world, my lived experiences taught me a lot about love and perseverance - despite always struggling with it lol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love to learn and live, I learn to live and love, and I live to love and learn.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hewwo World</title>
      <link>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 18:28:17 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pearrybyte.github.io/recordofmyyouth/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;hi guysssss :3 i am so happeh to have made this website!!! couldn&amp;rsquo;t have done it without namecrisis. everything is gonna be so awesome..! :D&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;hi guysssss :3 i am so happeh to have made this website!!! couldn&amp;rsquo;t have done it without namecrisis. everything is gonna be so awesome..! :D&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
